<all>

<and_my_youtube>
<en>and I also have a YouTube channel as</en>
<gr>και έχω επίσης κανάλι στο YouTube, με ψευδώνυμο</gr>
</and_my_youtube>
<alenas_is_greek>
<en>Alenas is what the word Greek sounds like in Greek.</en>
<gr>Alenas σημαίνει Έλληνας.</gr>
</alenas_is_greek>
<hello>
<en>
Welcome, I'm a fan of iterative creative processes and minimalism.
I've been through many phases, where I became obsessed with
the agile manifesto and then got punished for trying to inspire
teammates, or before that where I thought it's not necessary to
communicate with people and then I became obsessed with
face to face collaboration until people didn't want to follow,
and there have been many smaller opinion changes too.
I'm not fully shaped but I have started taking shape.
</en>
<gr>
Γενικά συμπαθώ την σταδιακή πρόοδο, δηλαδή να φτιάχνω πράγματα
στάδιο στάδιο αντί για κομμάτι κομμάτι, και είμαι μινιμαλιστής.
Ελπίζω να φαίνεται ότι έχω περάσει από πολλά στάδια και σαν
προσωπικότητα. Είχα πάθος με το agile manifesto για ένα διάστημα,
επίσης από εσωστρεφής γύρισα στο άλλο άκρο να προσπαθώ απεγνωσμένα
να συνεργαστώ πρόσωπο με πρόσωπο σε ενοχλητικό σημείο,
έχω αλλάξει και μερικές απόψεις όσο αφορά λογισμικό,
και κάθε φορά υπάρχει αυτή η έντονη αλλαγή από τη μία άποψη στην άλλη
μέχρι που το περιβάλλον με βάζει σε μία σειρά.
Έχω αρχίσει να σχηματίζομαι, αλλά έχω πολύ δρόμο ακόμα.
</gr>
</hello>
<for_hr>
<en>
I keep this website mainly for people who think of hiring me.
</en>
<gr>
Έφτιαξα αυτό τον ιστοχώρο κυρίως για εργοδότες.
</gr>
</for_hr>
<what_ive_done>
<en>
As of 2023, I don't have hands-on experience developing
websites and web apps except this site.
I've used various tools and techniques
for my personal environment,
and I'm surprisingly comfortable handling complexity
for an undergraduate.
</en>
<gr>
Μέχρι στιγμής, το 2023, δεν έχω πρακτική εμπειρία στις
διαδικτυακές εφαρμογές και ιστοχώρους εκτός από αυτόν εδώ,
αλλά έχω χρησιμοποιήσει μια μεγάλη ποικιλία εργαλείων και
έχω προγραμματίσει με διάφροες τεχνικές,
όσο φτιάχνω εργαλεία για το προσωπικό μου περιβάλλον.
Για τα δεδομένα προπτυχιακού φοιτητή
είμαι αρκετά άνετος με πολύπλοκα προβλήματα.
</gr>
</what_ive_done>
<lets_go_out>
<en>
If you're okay with it
I'd like to go outside with the developers
and have some fun talking and coding,
perhaps doing our warm ups or exercises.
Then we can all judge together if I fit and where I'd fit.
Of course I'll cover up for backlash from higher ups wherever I can
and if you're not willing anyway, I understand that.
</en>
<gr>
Αν συμφωνείτε θα χαιρόμουν να βγω με τους προγραμματιστές
και να συζητήσουμε ή να κάνουμε μαζί ασκήσεις ή προθέρμανση
αν τους ενδιαφέρουν αυτά.
Μετά μπορούμε να συμφωνήσουμε όλοι μαζί
αν ταιριάζω στην εταιρία και πού.
Εννοείται πως αν προκύψουν προβλήματα με ανώτερα στελέχη
θα συμπαρασταθώ όπου μπορώ, και αν δε θέλετε το καταλαβαίνω.
</gr>
</lets_go_out>
</all>
<!--
    Copyright (c) 2023 Dimakopoulos Theodoros

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
SOFTWARE.
-->
