<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<all>

<s n="find-me-on">
<en>You may find me on</en>
<gr>Για περισσότερα,</gr>
</s>
<s n="youtube">
<en>YouTube as Theodore Alenas or</en>
<gr>στο YouTube ονομάζομαι Theodore Alenas και</gr>
</s>
<s n="github">
<en>GitHub also as TheodoreAlenas,</en>
<gr>στο GitHub TheodoreAlenas.</gr>
</s>
<s n="email">
<en>or email me at dimakopt732@gmail.com.</en>
<gr>Το e-mail μου είναι dimakopt732@gmail.com.</gr>
</s>
<s n="active-on-youtube">
<en>
I produce about weekly content on YouTube
but I'm inactive on social media otherwise.
</en>
<gr>
Ανεβάζω βίντεο στο YouTube περίπου κάθε εβδομάδα,
αλλά κρατάω μια απόσταση από άλλα μέσα δικτύωσης.
</gr>
</s>
<s n="alenas-is-greek">
<en>Alenas is what the word Greek sounds like in Greek.</en>
<gr>Alenas σημαίνει Έλληνας, όπως alien, ale.</gr>
</s>
<s n="hello">
<en>
So, welcome! I'm a University student,
started on 2019, and I love programming.
I mostly tinker the operating system
on the lowest possible level every time
and I've been through the journey to Linux, NeoVim and Emacs.
Today I consider it to be a journey
to the different cultures of programmers,
because these tools have a history that belongs to
mathematicians, system administrators, low level programmers and so on.
</en>
<gr>
Οπότε, χαίρετε! Είμαι φοιτητής του 2019 και λατρεύω την πληροφορική.
Κυρίως ασχολούμαι με μικρά πράγματα του λειτουργικού συστήματος
στο χαμηλότερο δυνατό επίπεδο κάθε φορά
και έχω περάσει από το ταξίδι σε Linux, NeoVim και Emacs.
Το εκλαμβάνω σαν ταξίδι πλέον, γιατί αυτά τα εργαλεία έχουν
μια ιστορία που αφορά προγραμματιστές συγκεκριμένης κουλτούρας
όπως μαθηματικοί, system administrators, χαμηλού επιπέδου και λοιπά.
</gr>
</s>
<s n="im-minimalist">
<en>
I love minimalism and I move iteratively,
so that there is always something to demonstrate.
I've been through multiple iterations myself too.
I used to be obsessed with the agile manifesto,
also I switched from being closed
to obsessing over face to face collaboration to an annoying extent,
I've changed opinions regarding software too
and generally I'd rather be hurt now than get hurt making realizations.
I do find that all of this is nice but you may want
to keep in mind that I perform well among like minded people.
</en>
<gr>
Μου αρέσει ο μινιμαλισμός και εργάζομαι σε στάδια,
όπου σε κάθε στάδιο υπάρχει κάτι που θα μπορούσε να επιδείξει κανείς.
Έχω περάσει από πολλά στάδια και σαν προσωπικότητα.
Είχα πάθος με το agile manifesto για ένα διάστημα,
επίσης από κλειστός χαρακτήρας άρχισα να επιμένω
στη συνεργασία πρόσωπο με πρόσωπο σε ενοχλητικό σημείο,
έχω αλλάξει απόψεις όσο αφορά λογισμικό
και γενικά προτιμώ να πονέσω τώρα παρά να πονάω ανακαλύπτοντας.
Φυσικά έχει διπλή όψη αυτό το νόμισμα και προτιμώ να συνεργάζομαι
με άτομα που έχουμε κοινό τρόπο σκέψης.
</gr>
</s>
<s n="for-hr">
<en>
I keep this website mainly for people who think of hiring me.
</en>
<gr>
Έφτιαξα αυτό τον ιστοχώρο κυρίως για εργοδότες.
</gr>
</s>
<s n="what-ive-done">
<en>
As of 2023, I don't have hands-on experience developing
websites and web apps except this site.
I've used various tools and techniques
for my personal environment,
and I'm surprisingly comfortable handling complexity
for an undergraduate.
</en>
<gr>
Μέχρι στιγμής, το 2023, δεν έχω πρακτική εμπειρία στις
διαδικτυακές εφαρμογές και ιστοχώρους εκτός από αυτόν εδώ,
αλλά έχω χρησιμοποιήσει μια μεγάλη ποικιλία εργαλείων και
έχω προγραμματίσει με διάφροες τεχνικές,
όσο φτιάχνω εργαλεία για το προσωπικό μου περιβάλλον.
Για τα δεδομένα προπτυχιακού φοιτητή
είμαι αρκετά άνετος με πολύπλοκα προβλήματα.
</gr>
</s>
<s n="lets-go-out">
<en>
If you don't mind,
I'd like to go outside with the developers
and have some fun together and see it from there,
we can all judge together if I fit and where I'd fit.
I'll cover for backlash from higher ups.
</en>
<gr>
Αν συμφωνείτε θα χαιρόμουν να βγω με τους προγραμματιστές
και να το πάμε βλέποντας, να δούμε αν ταιριάζω και πού.
Αν προκύψουν προβλήματα με ανώτερα στελέχη σας καλύπτω.
</gr>
</s>
</all>
<!--
    Copyright (c) 2023 Dimakopoulos Theodoros <dimakopt732@gmail.com>

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
SOFTWARE.
-->
