<all>
<teo><en>Theodore</en><gr>Θοδωρής</gr></teo>
<dimak><en>Dimakopoulos</en><gr>Δημακόπουλος</gr></dimak>
<i_trust_reworks>
<en>
Welcome people! I've failed and rebuilt myself so much by now
that reworks are something I've come to trust.
</en>
<gr>
Χαίρετε! Χρειάστηκε να επανασχεδιάσω τη ζωή μου τόσο
που πλέον εμπιστεύομαι τους επανασχεδιασμούς.
</gr>
</i_trust_reworks>
<i_value_emotions>
<en>
Through this journey I've come to value observing emotions
over avoiding shame, and simplifying requirements over analyzing.
</en>
<gr>
Μέσα από αυτό το ταξίδι προτεραιοποίησα την κατανόηση συναισθημάτων
αντί της ντροπής και την απλοποίηση απαιτήσεων έναντι της ανάλυσης.
</gr>
</i_value_emotions>
<i_relax_coding>
<en>
Reworking my identity is draining, so I spend a lot of time
programming to relax, since I always had a head start in it.
</en>
<gr>
Η επανάχτιση του εαυτού μου είναι εξαντλητική, οπότε ξοδεύω
πολύ χρόνο προγραμματίζοντας για ανακούφιση, επειδή εκεί έχω προβάδισμα.
</gr>
</i_relax_coding>
<lets_go_out>
<en>
I keep this website mainly for people who think of hiring me.
As of 2023, I don't have hands-on experience developing
websites and web apps except this site.
I've used various tools and techniques
for my personal environment,
and I'm comfortable handling complexity given I'm undergraduate,
so I'd say if you're okay with it
I'd like to go outside with the developers
and have some fun talking and coding,
perhaps doing our warm ups or exercises.
Then we can all judge together if I fit and where I'd fit.
Of course I'll cover up for backlash from higher ups wherever I can
and I don't insist at all in this idea in general.
</en>
<gr>
Συντηρώ αυτό τον ιστοχώρο κυρίως για εργοδότες.
Μέχρι στιγμής, το 2023, δεν έχω πρακτική εμπειρία στις
διαδικτυακές εφαρμογές και ιστοχώρους εκτός από αυτόν εδώ.
Έχω χριησιμοποιήσει μια μεγάλη ποικιλία εργαλείων και τεχνικών
προγραμματισμού για το προσωπικό μου περιβάλλον,
και είμαι αρκετά άνετος στη διαχείριση πολυπλοκότητας
για τα δεδομένα προπτυχιακού φοιτητή,
οπότε αν δεν έχετε πρόβλημα θα χαιρόμουν να βγω με τους προγραμματιστές
και να συζητήσουμε ή να κάνουμε μαζί ασκήσεις ή προθέρμανση
αν τους ενδιαφέρουν αυτά.
Μετά μπορούμε να συμφωνήσουμε όλοι μαζί
αν ταιριάζω στην εταιρία και πού.
Εννοείται πως θα βοηθήσω στην κάλυψη από προβλήματα με ανώτερα στελέχη
όπου μπορώ, και ούτε επιμένω στην όλη ιδέα γενικότερα.
</gr>
</lets_go_out>
</all>
<!--
    Copyright (c) 2023 Dimakopoulos Theodoros

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
SOFTWARE.
-->
