<all>
<title><en>This website</en><gr>Αυτός ο ιστοχώρος</gr></title>
<body>
<en>
A pre-rendered site.
The first major version abstracted while the second abbreviated.
</en>
<gr>
Pre-rendered ιστοχώρος.
Η πρώτη κύρια έκδοση είχε αφαιρετικό κώδικα,
ενώ η δεύτερη συντόμευε μεγάλα κομμάτια κώδικα σαν συντομογραφίες.
</gr>
</body>
<had_menus>
<en>
Old versions of this site had typical menus at the top,
which would turn into drop down menus on mobile view,
or as they're called, hamburger menus.
A questionable
</en>
<gr>
Σε παλιότερες εκδόσεις του ιστοχώρου, τα μενού στην κορυφή
των σελίδων είχαν τη συνηθισμένη μορφοποίηση και σε μεγάλες
και σε μικρές οθόνες. Για μια μικρή επίδειξη,
σερβίρεται ακόμα μια
</gr>
</had_menus>
<older_version>
<en>older version</en>
<gr>πεπαλαιωμένη έκδοση</gr>
</older_version>
<is_still_served>
<en>of the biography page is still served for demonstration.</en>
<gr>του βιογραφικού. Το κείμενο ήταν σημαντικά χειρότερο τότε.</gr>
</is_still_served>
<find>
<en>You may find the</en>
<gr>Μπορείτε να βρείτε και την</gr>
</find>
<v1><en>first</en><gr>πρώτη</gr></v1>
<and><en>and</en><gr>και τη</gr></and>
<v2><en>second</en><gr>δεύτερη</gr></v2>
<on_gh><en>version on GitHub</en><gr>έκδοση στο GitHub</gr></on_gh>
<with>
<en>as well as it's</en>
<gr>καθώς και την</gr>
</with>
<v1>
<en>first version</en>
<gr>πρώτη του έκδοση</gr>
</v1>
<many_phases>
<en>
At first, the site was based on abstraction layers
and components that choose their identity from a buffee,
then the site became client-side rendered
with macros and served almost as-is,
then fully progressively enhanced for Emacs' browser,
then it lost its menus which got replaced with plain text.
The site got a simpler design over time
while preserving or enhancing various values.
The final design trivialises mobile support, old browser support,
accessibility, localization, theme switching and navigation.
It's fascinating that it looks neither better nor worse.
While it can't impress at first sight,
it gives the impression that it's going to be predictable
and it won't cause the user trouble.
</en>
<gr>
Η πρώτη φάση του ιστοχώρου βασιζόταν σε επίπεδα αφαίρεσης όπου
τα στοιχεία που εμφανίζονται επιλέγουν τις ιδιότητές τους
μέσα από ένα μπουφέ επιλογών. Η επόμενη φάση ήταν να σερβίρονται οι
ιστοσελίδες ως έχουν, χρησιμοποιώντας έναν αυτοσχέδιο μηχανισμό macros,
έπειτα χρησιμοποιήθηκε progressive enhancement για να στηρίζεται ο
περιηγητής του Emacs,
έπειτα αντικαταστάθηκαν τα μενού στην κορυφή από απλό κείμενο.
Απλοποιήθηκε δηλαδή ο σχεδιασμός του ιστοχώρου σταδιακά,
διατηρώντας όσο το δυνατόν περισσότερα θετικά.
Στην τελική του μορφή, απλοποιούνται σημαντικά κάποια ζητήματα όπως
η εμφάνιση σε μικρές οθώνες,
η υποστήριξη παλιών περιηγητών ή σύγχρωνων απλών περιηγητών,
η προσβασιμότητα από άτομα με ειδικές ανάγκες,
η εναλλαγή μεταξύ Ελληνικής και Αγγλικής γλώσσας,
η εναλλαγή μεταξύ  ανοιχτού και σκούρου θέματος
και η πλοήγηση μεταξύ των σελίδων.
Ενδιαφέρον είναι ότι η εμφάνιση άλλαξε έντονα
αλλά ούτε βελτιώθηκε ούτε χειροτέρευσε.
Δεν είναι εντυπωσιακή από πρώτη όψη,
αλλά δίνει την αίσθηση ότι είναι προβλέψιμη
και δε θα δημιουργήσει προβλήματα.
</gr>
</many_phases>
</all>
<!--
    Copyright (c) 2023 Dimakopoulos Theodoros <dimakopt732@gmail.com>

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
SOFTWARE.
-->
