<all>
<title><en>This website</en><gr>Αυτός ο ιστοχώρος</gr></title>
<body>
<en>
A pre-rendered site.
There have been numerous iterations and redesigns.
The first major version abstracted while the secord abbreviated.
</en>
<gr>
Pre-rendered ιστοχώρος.
Πέρασε από πολλούς επανασχεδιασμούς.
Η πρώτη κύρια έκδοση βασιζόταν σε αφαίρεση,
ενώ η δεύτερη σε συντομογραφίες.
</gr>
</body>
<had_menus>
<en>
Old versions of this site had typical menus at the top,
which would turn into drop down menus on mobile view,
or as they're called, hamburger menus.
An
</en>
<gr>
Σε παλιότερες εκδόσεις του ιστοχώρου, τα μενού στην κορυφή
των σελίδων είχαν τη συνηθισμένη μορφοποίηση και σε μεγάλες
και σε μικρές οθόνες. Για μια μικρή επίδειξη,
σερβίρεται ακόμα μια
</gr>
</had_menus>
<older_version>
<en>older version</en>
<gr>παλιότερη έκδοση</gr>
</older_version>
<is_still_served>
<en>of the biography page is still served for demonstration.</en>
<gr>της ιστοσελίδας του βιογραφικού.</gr>
</is_still_served>
<find>
<en>You may find the</en>
<gr>Μπορείτε να βρείτε και την</gr>
</find>
<v1><en>first</en><gr>πρώτη</gr></v1>
<and><en>and</en><gr>και τη</gr></and>
<v2><en>second</en><gr>δεύτερη</gr></v2>
<on_gh><en>version on GitHub</en><gr>έκδοση στο GitHub</gr></on_gh>
<with>
<en>as well as it's</en>
<gr>καθώς και την</gr>
</with>
<v1>
<en>first version</en>
<gr>πρώτη του έκδοση</gr>
</v1>
<many_phases>
<en>
As said, this website was rewritten numerous times,
first abstract with components that choose their identity from a buffee,
then client-side rendered with macros and served almost as-is,
then fully progressively enhanced for Emacs' browser,
then it lost its menus which got replaced with plain text.
That's a linear story going from a complex to a simple design,
while keeping as many positives as possible.
The final design trivialises mobile support, old browser support,
accessibility, localization, theme switching and navigation.
The fascinating part is that it looks neither better nor worse,
it's just different. Spectacularly different for that matter.
It gives off a feeling like a late night show or a poem.
It has very different values, it can't impress and it's
awkwardly unfamiliar, but ultimately this is how I am.
</en>
<gr>
Η πρώτη φάση του ιστοχώρου βασιζόταν σε επίπεδα αφαίρεσης όπου
τα στοιχεία που εμφανίζονται επιλέγουν τις ιδιότητές τους
μέσα από ένα μπουφέ επιλογών. Η επόμενη φάση ήταν να σερβίρονται οι
ιστοσελίδες ως έχουν, χρησιμοποιώντας έναν αυτοσχέδιο μηχανισμό macros,
έπειτα χρησιμοποιήθηκε progressive enhancement για να στηρίζεται ο
περιηγητής του Emacs, έπειτα αντικαταστάθηκαν τα μενού στην κορυφή
από απλό κείμενο. Αυτές οι αλλαγές οδηγούν σταδιακά από περίπλοκους
σε απλούς σχεδιασμούς, διατηρώντας όσο το δυνατόν περισσότερα θετικά.
Η τελική μορφή του ιστοχώρου απλοποιεί την υποστήριξη μικρών οθωνών,
την υποστήριξη παλιών ή απλών περιηγητών, την προσβασιμότητα,
την εναλλαγή γλωσσών, την εναλλαγή ανοιχτού/σκούρου θέματος
και την πλοήγηση.
Ενδιαφέρον είναι ότι η εμφάνιση ούτε βελτιώθηκε ούτε χειροτέρευσε.
Άλλαξε δραματικά βέβαια, από πιασάρικη σε ομιλιτική.
Πλέον δεν μπορεί να εντυπωσιάσει και δίνει μια άβολη αίσθηση του
αγνώστου, αλλά έτσι ακριβώς είμαι και εγώ.
</gr>
</many_phases>
</all>
<!--
    Copyright (c) 2023 Dimakopoulos Theodoros

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
SOFTWARE.
-->
