<all>
<title><en>Architecture</en><gr>Αρχιτεκτονική</gr></title>
<os>
<en>
Hasn't worked on a large enough system to experience
the impact of architectural decisions,
but there have been some noteworthy moments.
Because the operating system relied so much on the user,
any rewrites were done on a fundamental level,
experimenting with significantly varied ways of organizing complexity.
The directory structure holding projects and images,
the image tagging system
and the key bindings framework and command palette
were all reworked roughly speaking 5 times each.
At one point, images were placed in a binary tree of directories,
following manual decisions in the style of is it or is it not.
There was also a point where projects were categorized using symlinks,
and the key bindings system used to also play the role of
a code snippet system, which also allowed the user to manipulate
a code snippet, and perhaps execute it if it's a shell script.
Before that, the image tagging was done by
prepending letters to file names which acted like flags,
also the directory structure had chains of shell scripts
that lead from an outside directory deeper and deeper into the tree.
The experimentations give a sense of
what ideas are worth more attention. Generally speaking,
flatter hierarchies are better,
and one would rather exhaust all the technically simple solutions
before attempting a technically complicated one.
</en>
<gr>
Παρότι δεν έχει χειριστεί κάποιο αρκετά περίπλοκο σύστημα
ώστε να γίνει αισθητή η επιρροή των αρχιτεκτονικών αποφάσεων,
υπάρχουν ορισμένες αξιοσημείωτες ανακαλύψεις και εμπειρίες.
Ένας λόγος πίσω από αυτό είναι ότι το λειτουργικό σύστημα
βασίζεται σε μεγάλο βαθμό στο χρήστη, οπότε οι
πειραματισμοί και οι επανασχεδιασμοί
γίνονταν σε όσο το δυνατό πιο χαμηλό επίπεδο.
Η δομή των φακέλων των πρότζεκτ και των εικόνων,
το σύστημα κατηγοριοποίησης εικόνων
και το σύστημα συνδυασμού πλήκτρων
επανασχεδιάστηκαν περίπου 5 φορές το καθένα.
Για ένα διάστημα, οι εικόνες κατηγοριοποιούνταν μέσα σε ένα
δυαδικό δέντρο φακέλων. Ο χρήστης έκανε επιλογές τύπου
είναι ή δεν είναι, ώστε να διασχίσει τους φακέλους και να βρει
ή να τοποθετήσει μια εικόνα.
Υπήρξε επίσης ένα διάστημα που οι φάκελοι των πρότζεκτ
κατηγοριοποιούνταν με τη χρήση symlinks,
και το σύστημα συνδυασμού πλήκτρων αποθήκευε
τμήματα κώδικα παντός χρήσης, με τη δυνατότητα να τα επεξεργαστεί
πρωτού τα επικολλήσει ή τα εκτελέσει.
Πρωτύτερα, οι εικόνες κατηγοριοποιούνταν χρησιμοποιώντας
γράμματα στην αρχή του ονόματός τους
και υπήρχαν αλυσίδες από shell scripts που ξεκινούσαν από εξωτερικούς
φακέλους πρότζεκτ και κατέληγαν σε εσωτερικούς.
Τελικά, οι πιο επίπεδες ιεραρχίες είναι οι καλύτερες σε γενικές γραμμές,
και είναι πιο αποδοτικό να ψάχνει κανείς μεταξύ των τεχνικά απλών
λύσεων μέχρι να τις εξαντλήσει, πρωτού λάβει υπόψη τις πολυπλοκότερες.
</gr>
</os>
<values>
<en>
Through this journey, some ideas that proved to be valuable are
prototyping,
thinking in tradeoffs,
technical simplicity from high to low levels,
and the
</en>
<gr>
Μέσα από αυτά τα κινήματα, αποδείχτηκε χρήσιμα
τα προτότυπα,
η αίσθηση των υπέρ και κατά μιας ιδέας,
η τεχνική απλότητα και σε υψηλό και σε χαμηλό επίπεδο,
και το
</gr>
</values>
<manifesto>
<en>Manifesto for Agile Software Development</en>
<gr>Manifesto for Agile Software Development</gr>
</manifesto>
</all>
<!--
    Copyright (c) 2023 Dimakopoulos Theodoros

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
SOFTWARE.
-->
