<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<all>
<s n="title"><en>Architecture</en><gr>Αρχιτεκτονική</gr></s>
<s n="os">
<en>
Architecture may not be the best term since there is no
experience with large systems.
There have been however experiences of
creations that were used for a long time, with changing requirements.
The directory structure that holds projects and images
was reorganized five times,
similar to the image tagging system
and the key bindings framework and command palette.
At one point, images were placed in a binary tree of directories,
where the user would traverse the directories asking questions
in the style of is it or is it not,
in order to find or insert a new image.
There was also a point where projects were categorized using symlinks,
and the key bindings system used to also play the role of
a code snippet system, which also allowed the user to manipulate
a code snippet, and perhaps execute it if it's a shell script.
Before that, the image tagging was done by
prepending letters to file names which acted like flags,
also the directory structure had chains of shell scripts
that lead from an outside directory deeper and deeper into the tree.
Generally, flatter hierarchies proved to be the most effective approach.
</en>
<gr>
Αρχιτεκτονική ίσως να μην είναι ο πιο σωστός όρος,
αφού δεν έχει υπάρξει εμπειρία με μεγάλα συστήματα.
Υπάρχει όμως η αίσθηση ότι μία κατασκευή χρησιμοποιείται
για πολύ καιρό και οι απαιτήσεις της αλλάζουν.
Η δομή των φακέλων με πρότζεκτ και εικόνες
επανασχεδιάστηκε περίπου πέντε φορές,
όπως και το σύστημα κατηγοριοποίησης εικόνων
και το σύστημα συνδυασμού πλήκτρων.
Για ένα διάστημα, οι εικόνες κατηγοριοποιούνταν μέσα σε ένα
δυαδικό δέντρο φακέλων. Ο χρήστης έκανε επιλογές τύπου
είναι ή δεν είναι, ώστε να διασχίσει τους φακέλους και να βρει
ή να τοποθετήσει μια εικόνα.
Υπήρξε επίσης ένα διάστημα που οι φάκελοι των πρότζεκτ
κατηγοριοποιούνταν με τη χρήση symlinks,
και το σύστημα συνδυασμού πλήκτρων αποθήκευε
τμήματα κώδικα παντός χρήσης, με τη δυνατότητα να τα επεξεργαστεί
πρωτού τα επικολλήσει ή τα εκτελέσει.
Άλλοτε οι εικόνες κατηγοριοποιούνταν χρησιμοποιώντας
γράμματα στην αρχή του ονόματός τους
και για τα πρότζεκτ υπήρχαν αλυσίδες από shell scripts
που ξεκινούσαν από εξωτερικούς φακέλους και κατέληγαν σε εσωτερικούς.
Τελικά αποδείχτηκε ότι οι πιο επίπεδες ιεραρχίες είναι οι καλύτερες.
</gr>
</s>
<s n="values">
<en>
These relatively simple experiences proved prototyping to be valuable,
and they highlighted some positive and negative sides of
trees, hierarchies and multi purpose tools.
There were also many experimentations with abstract code
and code with tiny functions, and because some programs were very slow,
there were one or two painful experiments wich caching.
Since these programs were used constantly,
over time they revealed the messages behind the
</en>
<gr>
Αυτές οι σχετικά απλές εμπειρίες ανέδειξαν την αξία
της προτοτυποποίησης,
και έκαναν φανερά κάποια πλεονεκτήματα και μειονεκτήματα
των δένδρων, των ιεραρχιών και των εργαλείων πολλαπλής χρήσης.
Υπήρξαν διάφοροι πειραματισμοί και με αφαιρετικό κώδικα
και με πολύ μικρές συναρτήσεις,
και επειδή ορισμένα προγράμματα ήταν πολύ αργά,
υπήρξαν ένας ή δύο οδυνηροί πειραματισμοί με caching.
Επειδή αυτά τα προγράμματα χρησιμοποιούνταν,
γίνονταν όλο και πιο φανερά τα μηνύματα του
</gr>
</s>
<s n="manifesto"><en>Manifesto</en><gr>Manifesto</gr></s>
<s n="for-agile">
<en>for Agile Software Development.</en>
<gr>for Agile Software Development.</gr>
</s>
</all>
<!--
    Copyright (c) 2023 Dimakopoulos Theodoros <dimakopt732@gmail.com>

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
SOFTWARE.
-->
