<all>
<title><en>Friends</en><gr>Φίλοι</gr></title>
<psychotherapy>
<en>
Lived lonely and proud until the age of 21,
but eventually humbled and started
exercising the ability to attend to conversations
and gradually made some basic friendships.
</en>
<gr>
Μέχρι την ηλικία των 21 έζησε εσωστρεφής και περήφανος,
αλλά τελικά άλλαξε στάση και άρχισε να σχηματίζει
παρέες. Δεν ήταν εύκολο.
</gr>
</psychotherapy>
<collabs>
<en>
Collaborated with various people.
On one project we willingly worked next to each other
4 hours a day 4 days a week for 2 months,
rounding the numbers below the theoretical maximum.
That's 6 per 4 for 3.
That was the absolute best experience.
The worst project experiences came from
resistance to collaborate.
</en>
<gr>
Συνεργάστηκε με διάφορα άτομα,
και η καλύτερη συνεργασία έγινε με νέους τότε φίλους,
πρόσωπο με πρόσωπο
4 ώρες τη μέρα 4 μέρες την εβδομάδα επί 2 μήνες,
στρογγυλοποιώντας κάτω από το θεωρητικό μέγιστο
6 ανά 4 επί 3.
Οι πιο δυσάρεστες εμπειρίες συνεργασίας σε εργασίες της σχολής
προέρχονταν από αντίσταση στη συνεργασία.
</gr>
</collabs>
<everyone_hates_me>
<en>
The truth is that with most of the teams
I've collaborated with in the University, we don't talk anymore.
The adrenaline fuelled, their followers,
those who hibernate to survive those who only order and critisize,
none of them appreciate calm collaboration.
There were a few nice collaborations however.
I'm having to understand that
if someone uses stress for motivation I can't calm them down,
because they'll lose their motivation and they'll perceive that
as giving a problem.
I can only demonstrate my way of working and let them think about it,
which they'll hopefully perceive as a solution to a problem.
</en>
<gr>
Η αλήθεια είναι ότι από τις ομάδες που συνεργαστήκαμε στο Πανεπιστήμιο,
με τις περισσότερες δε μιλάμε πλέον.
Ενέργεια απ' το άγχος, οι ακόλουθοί τους,
οι παράλυτοι που επιβιώνουν την κριτική των τρελών,
λίγοι εκτιμούν την ήρεμη συνεργασία.
Ορισμένες συνεργασίες ήταν καλές πράγματι.
Είναι δώρο άδωρο να καταλάβω ότι αν ο συνάδελφος
παίρνει ενέργεια μέσα από το άγχος δεν μπορώ να τον ηρεμήσω,
γιατί θα χάσει την ενέργειά του και θα εκλάβει ότι του έφερα προβλήματα.
Μπορώ μόνο να διαφημίσω τον δικό μου τρόπο δουλειάς και να τον αφήσω
να το σκεφτεί, που ίσως το εκλάβει σαν λύση σε πρόβλημα.
</gr>
</everyone_hates_me>
</all>
<!--
    Copyright (c) 2023 Dimakopoulos Theodoros

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
SOFTWARE.
-->
